

# **SOFIA KASIMI**

## **UX-UI Designer/ Frontend Designer**

#### ABOUT ME

Creative UX Designer living in Amsterdam with experience in designing and developing real-world applications.

My passion is expanding worldwide by interacting with real-life use cases and get valuable insights for my design decisions.

Having applied knowledge in web front-end development, I understand systems and their limitations and can help to smooth the process between conceptualization and implementation.



sofiakas02@gmail.com



+31 687128060



https://sofiaux-.github.io/portfolio-website/

#### SOFTWARE

ADOBE SUITE A R 10





SKETCH/FIGMA 💝 🖡



BALSAMIQ (3)

ATOM ₩

GITHUB 🞧

### LANGUAGES

**GREEK** 



**ENGLISH** 

**DUTCH** 

GERMAN ●●



#### HOBBIES





MOVIES







## EXPERIENCE

2019-Present O UX DESIGNER / ST-ARTAMSTERDAM

UX designer for a Start-up company

- Competitor Analysis
- Information Architecture (IA) of the app
- Prototyping (low-mid-high Fidelity)

2018-2019

**ACADEMIC EXPERIENCE / SOFIAUX** 

Frontend developer for Careerfoundry

- · Develop a responsive portfolio website with HTML5, CSS, JS by using Atom and Github tools
- Experienced in JQuery script and media Queries

2018-2019

**ACADEMIC EXPERIENCE / INKTANK** 

**UX** Designer for Careerfoundry

- Collaborated with high experienced mentors to design a user centered native app
- · User Research / User Personas / User flows
- Design interactive low-high fidelity prototypes
- Conduct Usability testing

2012-2018

O FREELANCER GRAPHIC DESIGNER

Logo designer & Book Illustrator

- Logo design accompanied with Brand Book
- Typography savvy in digital products



### EDUCATION

2018-2019

**CAREERFOUNDRY GMBH** 

**UX Design / Frontend Development** 

- UX / UI responsive app from scratch with industry leading mentors
- Market research for user-centered product
- Web app development using HTML, CSS, JS

2007-2010

**VAKALO ART ACADEMIE** 

BA of Art / Graphic Design